goonj.pk 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | Goonj

**What is this Privacy Policy for?**

This privacy policy is served by  **Goonj**  for [www.goonj.pk](http://www.goonj.pk/) , [www.goonj.com.pk](http://www.goonj.com.pk/) (the  **“Website”** ) and [bit.ly/goonjapp](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.dmdmax.telenor&hl=en) (the **“App”** ). This policy governs the privacy of its users who choose to use the website and app.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website & app, and website & app owners. Furthermore the way this website and app processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

**The Website and Application**

This website and application and their owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience.

**Use of Cookies**

This website and app uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting Goonj. Where applicable, this website and app uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website and app to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer/device.

Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computer’s hard drive or device’s storage that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website and app. This allows the website and app, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within the website and app.

Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website or app on to their computers hard drive and device storage, they should take necessary steps within their web browsers and device security settings to block all cookies from this website, app and its external serving vendors.

This website and app uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use the services. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive or device storage in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website and app, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google’s privacy policy here for further information [http://www.google.com/privacy.html].

Other cookies may be stored to your computer’s hard drive or device storage by external vendors when this website or app uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

**Contact & Communication**

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but users using such form to email processes are advised that they do so at their own risk.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products/services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you (the consumer) have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.

**External Links**

Although this website and app only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website and app.

The owners of this website and app cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and app and their owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Advertisements and Sponsored Links**

This website and app may contain sponsored links and advertisements. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, who may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the ads they serve.

Clicking on any such advertisement will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website and app. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computer’s hard drive or device storage. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and app and their owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Social Media Platforms**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and app and their owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. Neither this website and app nor their owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website and app may use social sharing buttons which helps share web and app content directly from web or app pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**Shortened Links in Social Media**

This website and app and their owners through their social media platform accounts may share links to relevant web pages. By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy URLs or we may shorten URLs ourselves for ease of use and tracking clicks (this is an example: http://bit.ly/goonjapp).

Users are advised to take caution and good judgment before clicking any shortened URLs published on social media platforms by this website, app and their owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine URLs are published, many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and app and their owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.
